/*quiz_data2 */

const questions = [
    {
//214問目
question:"open(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["開いている","望む","～の間","超える"],
correctAnswer: "開いている"
    },
    {
//225問目
question:"believe(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["とても","感じる","信じる","生徒"],
correctAnswer: "信じる"
    },
    {
//229問目
question:"love(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["愛","申し出る","あなた","線"],
correctAnswer: "愛"
    },
    {
//241問目
question:"lead(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["起こる","信じる","～と","導く"],
correctAnswer: "導く"
    },
    {
//247問目
question:"hour(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["この","動かす","もっと","時間"],
correctAnswer: "時間"
    },
    {
//256問目
question:"reason(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["まだ","理由","動かす","政府"],
correctAnswer: "理由"
    },
    {
//261問目
question:"learn(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["～できる","だけれども","学ぶ","今"],
correctAnswer: "学ぶ"
    },
    {
//267問目
question:"enough(副詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["同じ","十分","なに","質問する"],
correctAnswer: "十分"
    },
    {
//273問目
question:"whether(接続詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["持っていく","長い","プログラム","～かどうか"],
correctAnswer: "～かどうか"
    },
    {
//283問目
question:"low(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["置く","低い","必要とする","学ぶ"],
correctAnswer: "低い"
    }
];

export default questions;

